Eight o'clock sharp.
（ホイスト）２０時ジャスト。　相変わらず
時間に正確ですね…　ダウト様。
You're as punctual as ever,
Sir Doubt.
（足音）
（ミゼルカ）早くしなさい　メランコリィ。
Hurry up, Melancholy!
（メランコリィ）
ハァ　ハァ　待ってよ！　お姉様！
Slow down, Sister!
（ミゼルカ）ごめんなさい。　この子の
支度に　手間取ってしまって…。
Forgive us for being late. Her preparations took longer than I expected.
（ホイスト）いえいえ。
私どもも　今　来たところですよ。
Please, worry not. We also just arrived recently,
ミゼルカ様　メランコリィ様。
Lady Mizerka, Lady Melancholy.
ねえ　お姉様。　このお花
似合ってますかしら？　ねえねえ。
Sister, what do you think? Does this flower fit me well?
Does it?
（ダウト）時間の無駄だ。
早く本題に入れ。　ミスター　ホイスト。
Stop wasting time. Cut to the chase, Mr. Whist.
何よ！
私は　無駄なものが嫌いでね。
Wha'd you say?!
I hate being wasteful.
（ピノクル）
日本は　かわいい子が多いね。
Japan is full of beautiful ladies!
見とれてたら
遅くなっちゃったんだ。
I was so entranced by them that I ended up being late.
Ladies, please accept this token of my apology.
これ　お嬢様たちへの
おわびのしるし。
結構よ。
下品な　お花！
No, thanks.
Flowers are disgusting.
People who break promises by arriving late,
約束に遅れ　他人の時間を
無駄にするような人間も→
約束より　早く来て　自分の時間を
and people who waste their time by arriving early,
私に言わせれば　愚か者だ。
are both fools in my eyes.
（ピノクル）
お　遅れてごめん　フリーセル…。
Sorry for being late, Freecell.
（フリーセル）遅れて
約束を破るくらいなら→
I still think it's better to be early and waste time
早く来て　時間を無駄にする方が
よっぽどいい。
than to be late and break a promise.
約束は　必ず守らなきゃね。
うっ。
We must keep our promises, no matter what.
（ホイスト）
皆様　おそろいになりましたので→
Ladies and gentlemen, please forgive my rudeness,
これより　お言葉を
お伝えいたします。
but I must convey a message to you.
A message from the leader of the Orpheus Order, Lord Clondike.
（ホイスト）我ら　オルペウス・オーダーの指導者
クロンダイク様からの　お言葉です。
lost te saguri de sagashiteta
Lost, trying to find it blindly with my hands.
tozasareta mirai no kotae nante doko ni mo nai
But the key to the locked future is nowhere to be found.
hashiru shoudou ima kaidoku funou
Undecipherable urges surging.
found kudaketa hazu no unmei wo
I found the fate I believed broken.
mijukuna yume no naka de kikoetekitan da
I heard it in my immature dream.
saigo made I'll be there for you
I'll be there for you till the very end.
tachitomaranai kono hari dake wa
I can't stop. I hear nothing else.
boku no asu wo kizamu oto tsukisasu
How this needle carves my future.
shinjitsu kara nigetara ima
I'm running away from the truth now.
genjitsu ni mo maketara ima
I'm losing to reality now.
nani ga nokoru no (nokoru no)
What will be left?
kazoekirenai kono kizu dake ga
The countless scars on my body
boku no kinou wo zanzou toshite kataru
are the only thing telling the story of my past.
unmei ga hodokete mo ima
Even if fate falls apart now,
sonzai wo kowashite mo ima
even if existence shatters now,
boku no michi wo yuku yo
I'm walkng down my own path.
It's now or never.
This is what they say: "Live your life today."
There will always be, there will always be a way.
Night of the Knights
あっ？！　ちょっと～！
あっ　うわっ！
Hey, wait!
違う！　あんたたち！
This isn't it!
You there!
うわ～！　う～っ！
う～。　これも違う！
This isn't it either!
（カイト）おい　ノノハ。
さっきから　何やってんだよ？
Hey, Nonoha...
What exactly are you doing?
決まってるでしょ！
I'm looking for students with rings, of course!
リングをつけてる子がいないか
探してるのよ。
はぁ？！
あのオルペウスの腕輪そっくりな
イヤリングや指輪で→
Airi and the vice president went through so much trouble
副会長も　アイリちゃんも
ひどい目にあったんでしょう！
because of those Orpheus ring accessories!
Cubie is analyzing the remains of the rings,
キューちゃんは　リングの残骸の分析を
続けてくれてるし→
and Ana asked his friends to check around town too.
So if you find anyone with accessories like that, let me know, okay?
アナも　お友達に頼んで
町じゅう　探してくれてる。
（アナ）教えてくれる？
副会長と　アイリちゃんだって…。
Even Airi and the vice president...
（タマキ）お願いします。
（アイリ）お願いしま～す。
Take one, please!
Please take one!
（タマキ）お願いします。
（女子生徒）フクロウ？
Take this, please.
An owl?
（アイリ）フクロウのアクセサリーです。
つけると　大変なんです。
Owl accessories! They have a horrible effect on people!
（タマキ）そもそも　アクセサリーを
つける事自体　校則違反ですけど。
Although it is against the rules to wear accessories in the first place.
とにかく　見かけたら
すぐにお知らせください！
But if you see any, please tell us right away.
So you should loo-
というわけで　カイトも探し…！
おっ。
Hey, your hairband...!
ちょっと！　そのカチューシャ！
やれやれ！
Give me a break...
あ～！　なんか疲れた。
よしよし…。
I'm beat.
There, there.
そりゃ　こ～んな顔して
歩いてりゃ　疲れるっつうの。
That's because you're running around making this face.
だってさぁ。
But that's because...
（ソウジ）何か　わかったかい？
キュービック君。
Have you figured anything out, Cubic?
These seem to be different from Kaito and Rook's Orpheus Armbands.
（キュービック）どうやら　カイトやルークの
オルペウスの腕輪とは違うものだね。
どういうことだ？
What do you mean?
In the fragments, I found traces of microchips that were developed very recently.
残骸の中に　ごく最近開発された
マイクロチップが混じっていた。
ごく最近？
うん。
Very recently?
Yeah. The Orpheus Armbands are supposed to be ancient relics.
オルペウスの腕輪は　太古の遺物のはず。
ということは…。
This means...
オルペウス・オーダーが作った
腕輪の偽物ってことかい？
These are just fakes that the Orpheus Order made?
（キュービック）
レプリカと言った方が　正確かな。
More like replicas.
But why would they do that?
なんで　そんなものを？
パズルが上手になりたいのかな？
They want to get better at puzzles?
データの収集って言ってたけど…。
気になるね。
They said they're collecting data.
That peeked my interest too.
どんなつもりだろうと　関係ねえ。
I don't care about their reasons.
パズルで人を傷つけるようなやつらは
絶対　許さねえ！
If they hurt people with puzzles, they'll have to deal with me!
Agreed! One vote for Kaito!
（アナ）賛成！　アナ　カイトに１票！
僕も。
うん！
Me too!
Yeah!
（ギャモン）まっ　ジタバタしたって
始まらねえぜ。
Well, we're not getting anywhere just talking about it.
（アナ・キュービック・ノノハ）ん？
手がかりが欲しけりゃ→
If we want clues, we should just wait for someone to fall victim to the rings again.
また誰かが　リングをはめられるのを
待てばいい。
Gammon! If that happens, their lives will be in danger!
ギャモン君！　リングをはめられたら
命だって危ないんだよ！
俺たちが　パズルで
勝ちゃいいんだろう？
We only need to solve the puzzles, right?
そうすりゃ　外れる。　すげえパズル
作ってくれるってんなら→
Then they come off.
If they make such badass puzzles, why not just enjoy the show?
せいぜい　楽しませてもらおうぜ。
ギャモン君！　全く…。
Gammon! Seriously...
ギャモンの言う事も　一理あるかもな。
He's got a point.
（アナ・ノノハ）はぁ？
カイトまで何を？！
What are you saying, Kaito?
Either way, they won't just stay put at this point.
どのみち　あいつらが　このまま
おとなしくしてるとは思えねえ…。
あぁ　ちょ　ちょっと！
Hey! Show me your watch!
腕時計　見せて！
はぁ？！
Huh?
だから　いいかげんに
しろってえの。
I told you to give it a break.
はぁ…　ったく…。
Man...
It's him!
あいつは？！
どうしたの？
（キュービック）カイト！　大変だ！
What's wrong?
Kaito! I've got bad news!
I analyzed the rings and searched for their signals.
オルペウス・リングを分析して
反応を探していたんだ。
そしたら…。
うそっ？！　これ　全部　リングの反応？！
Look!
No way! Those are all rings?
オルペウス・オーダーが　町じゅうの人たちに
ばらまいたんだ。
The Orpheus Order spread them all over town!
We've gotta hurry and find them all!
急いで回収しなくちゃ。
無理だよ　こんなに　たくさん。
That's impossible! There's too many!
でも…。
待て！　こいつは　パズルだ。
But...
Wait! This is a puzzle!
（２人）えっ？！
これらの点滅には
３つのパターンがある。
There are three groups of lights flashing.
そいつを３つ重ねて
全ての点をつなげると…。
If you overlap them and connect the dots, you get...
（キュービック）矢印！
この矢印が指している点は…。
Arrows!
The arrows all point to the same place.
あっ！
この場所って　まさか？！
No way, that's...
フン。
ただいま！　ミハル　帰ったぞ！
I'm home! Hey, Miharu!
あっ　お帰り！　お兄ちゃん。
Welcome home, Gammon!
Tonight's dinner will be your favorite and my specialty, spicy tomato dumplings!
今日の夕食は　ミハルの大好物
俺様特製　トマトスパイシー餃子！
ねえ　お兄ちゃん。
これ　どうかな？
Hey, Gammon... What do you think?
ギャモン！
ギャモン君！
Gammon!
やっぱり　ギャモン君の
マンションだったんだね。
So it was your mansion.
大変なの。　この中にいる誰かが
オルペウス・リングを…。
There's trouble! Someone in the building has an Orpheus ring...
あっ！　そいつは？！
えっ？！　あっ！
That's...
あいつら　妹に…　ミハルに　リングを…。
Those fuckers... They gave it to Miharu.
えっ？！
それで？！
Is she...?
She's fine, but they're not getting away with this.
無事だ。　許せねえ…。
ミハルまで巻き込みやがって。
For even trying to hurt Miharu...
許せねえ！
（腕輪の壊れる音）
They'll pay!
Gammon...
ギャモン君…。
リングと一緒に置いてあったってよ！
This was together with the ring.
To the Phi Brain children,
「ファイ・ブレインの子供たちへ。
ニッポン　ドーム　スタジアム　１８時。　ゲームスタート」。
Nippon Dome Stadium.
The game begins at 18:00.
俺たちへの…　招待状だ…。
It's our invitation!
ばらまかれたオルペウス・リングは？
大丈夫。
What about the rings all around town?
Don't worry. They were just dummy signal emitters.
全部　ダミーの発信装置だったよ。
18:05. You're five minutes late.
（ダウト）１８時５分。　５分の遅刻だな。
（ミゼルカ）パズルは解けたみたいね。
Looks like you solved the puzzle.
It was my little game. I hope you liked it.
（メランコリィ）
ちょっとした演出だったけど
気に入っていただけたかしら？
Why did you call us here?
こんな所に呼び出して
どういうつもりだ！
オルペウスの腕輪のレプリカを作り
うちの生徒を危険にさらした。
You made Orpheus Ring replicas and put our students in danger.
その理由も聞かせてもらいたいね。
（フリーセル）フッ…　言ったでしょう？
I want to know why.
I told you. We want to free humankind from the chains of the gods.
人間を　神々の　くびきから
解放するって。
お前…。
レプリカ・リングを使ってかい？
You...
By using replica rings?
Oh, please. We're making a perfect replica.
まさか…
究極のレプリカ・リングを作るのさ。
あっ！　人工的に　オルペウスの腕輪と
同じ能力を持つリングを→
You want to artificially produce a ring that has the same powers as the Orpheus Armbands?
作り出そうっていうの？！
えっ？！
Huh?
そうか。　今までのことは
そのための実験。
実験って？！
I see! So the ones from before were just experiments.
What do you mean?
副会長や　アイリに渡したのは
データ採集用のレプリカ・リングってことさ。
The rings they gave Airi and the vice president were just replicas for data collection.
なるほど。　２人を使って→
So that's how it was. You used those two to gather information in order to perfect your ring.
より本物の腕輪に近づけるための
データを集めていたってわけか…。
（拍手）
（ピノクル）よくできました。
Smart boy!
（ミゼルカ）
レプリカ・リングで　脳を強制活性化させた
者たちを　大門カイトにぶつける。
We make people with forcibly accelerated brains fight Daimon Kaito.
（メランコリィ）
強い相手と戦えば戦うほど
いいデータが取れるのよね　お姉さま。
The stronger the opponent, the better the data we get. Right, Sister?
That's so cruel!
それって　ひどい！
究極のレプリカ・リング…。
A perfect replica ring, huh? Why are you trying to make such a thing?
そんなものを作り出して　一体
何をしようっていうんだい？
（ダウト）世界中の人間に
分け与えてやるのだ。
We are going to distribute them to the people of the world.
そうすれば　全ての人間が
その封じられた力を→
Then every human will be able to awaken their sealed potential.
覚醒させることができる。
（キュービック）腕輪を使って
人間の能力を　強制的に→
Do you want to forcibly raise human performance by using those rings?
引き上げようっていうの？
（メランコリィ）導きますのよ　人類を。
We are going to lead humankind.
（フリーセル）
でも　実験は　しばらくお休み。
But we're putting our experiments on hold for a while.
We're starting a new game.
（ピノクル）新しいゲームを始めるよ。
（ミゼルカ）新しいゲーム。　それは…。
A new game, that is...
（ダウト）大門カイト。　お前を倒すこと。
...to defeat you, Daimon Kaito.
What?
なんだと？！
（ライトのつく音）
What is that?
これは…。
（ホイスト）ゲームに勝利しないかぎり
帰ることはできません。
You can't leave until you win.
フリーセル様たちも　ご存じない
新作パズルゲームをご用意いたしました。
I have prepared a new game that not even our members know about.
（メランコリィ）退屈だったら
承知しませんわよ　ホイ。
I won't play if it's boring, Wii.
ホイストでございます。
My name is Whist.
きっと　ご満足していただけると
思いますよ。　メラ様。
I am confident it will satisfy you, Lady Mela.
あぁ。　メ・ラ・ン・コ・リィ！
Me-lan-cho-ly!
（ホイスト）ごあいさつが遅れました。
I have yet to introduce myself.
私　フリーセル様たちの身の回りの
お世話をさせて頂いております→
I attend the affairs of these ladies and gentlemen.
ホイストと申します。
以後　お見知りおきを…。
My name is Whist. A pleasure to make your acquaintance.
（ホイスト）このゲームでは４対４に分かれ
陣地を奪い合っていただきます。
In this game, two teams of four people must fight over control of the board.
名付けて「ライトニング　ポジション」。
I call it "Lightning Position".
大門カイト様たちは　レッドチーム。
ダウト様たちは　ブルーチーム。
Sir Kaito and his friends are the red team.
Sir Doubt and his fellows are the blue team.
双方が　５手打ち　交代。
You make five moves, then switch.
次の方は　前の陣地を引き継ぎ
ゲームを続けていただきます。
The next person continues to expand that area.
チーム内で相談すること　アドバイスを
与え合うことは禁止とします。
You may not converse or offer advice during the game.
The team loses will...
敗北したチームの方々は…。
（ホイスト）このようになります。
end up like that.
また…　人殺しのパズルかよ。
Another murderous puzzle...
（口笛）
全く。　悪趣味ね　ホイは。
You sure have a warped mind, Wii.
カイト…　みんな…。
Kaito... Guys...
僕と君もいるのに　なんで
５対５じゃないのかな？
If you and I are both here, why isn't it 5v5?
君に参加する資格はないよ。
どういう意味だい？
You're not qualified to play.
What do you mean?
You weren't chosen by the ring.
君は　リングに選ばれなかった。
ファイ・ブレインになる可能性は
ないよね？
You don't have the possibility of becoming a Phi Brain.
大門カイト…。
ファイ・ブレインに限りなく近づいた男…。
Daimon Kaito, the man who almost reached the Phi Brain.
（ダウト）ファイ・ブレイン…　それは
神々の　くびきから解放され→
Phi Brains are people who have been released from their chains, and have awakened to their true power.
人が本来　持っている真の力に
目覚めた者…。
君を倒せば　俺たちも
ファイ・ブレインになれるかもってわけ。
If we defeat you, we may become Phi Brains as well.
You want to become Phi Brains?
お前らが　ファイ・ブレインに？！
（ダウト）
私たちも　ファイ・ブレインの子供なのだ。
We are children of the Phi Brain as well.
オルペウス・リングに選ばれた。
何？！
We have been chosen by the rings.
What?
（一同）あっ？！
あっ！　あれは？
Those...
軸川先輩　あれって…。
オ　オルペウスの腕輪…。
Jikugawa, are those...?
Orpheus Armbands.
レプリカなんかじゃないよ。
僕たちのは　正真正銘　本物さ。
And they're not replicas either.
Those are the real things.
You're all children of the Phi Brain too, right?
君たちも
ファイ・ブレインの子供なんでしょ？
一緒に頑張ろうよ。
Let's enjoy the game then!
リングは持っていないけれど～。
ウッ　フフフッ　フフフッ。
You don't have any rings though.
ウフッ。　レッツ　プレー　アップ。
Let's play up!
うふっ。
うっ。
どうぞ。
Call it.
う　裏…。
Tails.
（ホイスト）表…。
先攻は　メランコリィ様　ブルーチームです。
Heads. Lady Melancholy of the blue team moves first.
（ホイスト）それでは　ファーストゲーム　プレー！
The first game will now begin. Play!
参りますわよ。
Here I go!
（ホイスト）
プレーヤーは　チェスのナイトと同じ動き
四方の桂馬跳びで移動します。
The players move in jumps like the knight in chess.
（ホイスト）
移動した場所から　縦　横　斜め→
From there, they claim all panels
８方向のパネルを　自分の色に
変えることができます。
that are vertical, horizontal, and diagonal of that point.
If an opponent panel is blocking the way,
進んだ先に相手のパネルがあれば
１つだけ自分のものとし→
the player gains control of that panel, but cannot expand any further.
そこで止まります。
（ホイスト）
すでに自分の色となっているパネルは
そのまま進んでいきます。
If one of your own panels is in the way, it will keep expanding.
（ホイスト）
ファーストゲーム。　ウィナー　メランコリィ様！
First game: the winner is Lady Melancholy.
まぁ～！
全く…。　相手になりませんわね。
You really are no match.
それでは　ごきげんよう。
If you'll excuse me then....
ごめん…　みんな。
なあに　まだまだ挽回できるって。
I'm sorry, guys.
Don't worry, we can turn this around.
≪（ミゼルカ）私の相手は誰かしら？
（一同）あぁ？！
Who will be my opponent?
じゃあ　アナが行く。
My turn!
頼んだぜ　アナ！
（ブザー）
We're counting on you!
（ホイスト）セカンドゲーム。　ウィナー　ミゼルカ様。
Second game: the winner is Lady Mizerka.
アナ　お顔を作ろうと思ったんだけど
うまくできなかった。
I wanted to make a smiley face, but it didn't work out.
あぁ…　とにかく行ってくる。
Whatever. I'll go next.
へぇ～？！　君は　最後に
出てくるのかと思ったけど…。
Ha, I thought you'd come last.
「どうしても！」って　頼まれてな。
He asked me to.
Well, the order doesn't matter.
まっ　順番なんか
関係ないけどね…。
女の子だったら　優しくして
あげるんだけどな…。　フフフフッ。
Although if you were a girl, I'd be gentle.
（ホイスト）サードゲーム。　プレー！
（ブザー）
Third game, play.
フン。
行くぜ！
Here I go!
If we take the opponent's territory, they'll just take it back.
相手の陣地を　普通に
心の声
取っても　また取り返されるだけ。
このままじゃ　らちが明かねぇ！
This is getting nowhere.
そうか…。
心の声
（ブザー）
I see.
（ホイスト）サードゲーム。　ウィナー　ピノクル様！
Third game: the winner is Sir Pinochle!
１０ポイント差まで追い上げた。
カイト　偉～い！
We're now just ten points behind!
Go, Kaito!
Great as always, Kaito!
さっすが　カイト！
しかし…。
But...
Pinochle, that hurt to watch.
ピノクル…　ぶざまだな。
最低！
Pathetic.
しかも　最後の一手は
大門カイトのミスだわ。
And Daimon Kaito made a mistake on the last one.
A mistake? Really?
ミス？！　そうなんですか？
確かに　他の場所に
移動していれば→
He could have gotten more area if he had moved to a different spot.
もっと多くの陣地を
取れたはずだけど…。
おかげで助かったよ…　大門カイト君。
Thanks for the help, Daimon Kaito.
Kaito made a mistake? That can't be.
カイトがミス…　そんなことって…。
うふっ。
Sakanoue Gammon.
逆之上ギャモン。
He was chosen by Rook Banjo Crossfield...
ルーク・盤城・クロスフィールドに
見いだされた男。
大門カイトを　ファイ・ブレインに
育てるための踏み台として…。
...as a steppingstone for Daimon Kaito to reach the Phi Brain.
Your whole existence is a waste.
（ダウト）貴様の存在そのものが
無駄だな。　さっさと終わらせるぞ。
Let's end it here.
それでは　ラストゲーム。　プレー。
（ブザー）
The last game will now begin. Play.
妹が世話になった礼
させてもらうぜ。
I'll give you my thanks for taking good care of my sister.
Your sister? Oh, you mean that?
（ダウト）妹？　あぁ　あれのことか。→
I couldn't care less what happened to her.
別に　どうなろうと
知ったことではない。
なにっ？！　ケッ。
What?!
Although if it helps us achieve our goal,
（ダウト）むしろ　我々の大いなる
目的のために　役に立てたのなら→
then I must admit even her dull life has a meaning.
あの　つまらぬ命にも→
少しは生まれた意味が
あったというものだ。
ケッ。　なら　てめえには
生まれた事を後悔させてやるぜ！
Then I'll make you regret you were even born!
生まれて　俺と出会ったことをな！
And that you had to face me!
フン。
追いついた！
We caught up!
Dammit!
クソ…。
また離された…。
They got ahead again!
心の声
打てる手は　５とおり。
一番多く　パネルが取れるのは…。
I can move to five different spots.
I can take the most panels...
ここだぁ！
Here!
あっ！
これは？！　引き分け…。
It's...
a draw!
（ミゼルカ）ホイスト！　どういうこと？
What's the meaning of this, Whist?
本日のゲームは
引き分けとしておきましょう。
Today's game ends in a draw.
やっぱり　カイトは　すごいな。
どういう意味だい？
Kaito's really amazing.
What do you mean?
ミスしたんだよ。　彼。
He made a mistake!
Even if you take panels, the opponent will just take them back.
パネルの色を変えても
すぐに奪い返されちゃう。
そんなことを繰り返していても
意味ないよね。
There's no point in repeating that.
ほう。
そう…。
So instead of taking as many panels as he could,
だから　カイトは
数を多く取ることよりも→
奪い返されにくいパネルを
取ることを優先させたのさ。
Kaito took panels that are hard to take back instead.
ゲーム盤の端のパネルをね。
そのパネルは　最後まで　赤のままさ。
The border panels of the board.
Those panels stayed red all along.
I see!
そういうことか！
ミスしたわけじゃなかったんだ。
So it wasn't a mistake!
（キュービック）さっすが　カイト！
（アナ）やっぱり　偉い！
You're great, Kaito!
Really amazing!
カイトは　バカだがよ
なめねえ方がいいと思うぜ。
Kaito may be a dumbass, but don't underestimate him.
バカだがな。
バカバカ　うるせえな！
Even though he is a dumbass.
Stop calling me a dumbass!
Daimon Kaito...
大門カイト。
相変わらずだな。
He's still the same.
本当…　昔のままね…。
むかつくところが…。
Indeed. Just like back then.
He's just as annoying.
何の話だ？
What are you talking about?
まだ…　思い出せない？
思い…　出せない…？
You still can't remember?
Remember what?
また会おうね　カイト。
Let's meet again, Kaito.
みんな！
カイト！
Guys!
Kaito!
ママ…　カイトは
何も変わってなかったよ…。
Mama, Kaito hasn't changed a bit.
あの頃と同じように…
パズルが上手で→
He's just as good with puzzles as he was back then.
あの頃と同じように…
残酷だった。
He's just as merciless as he was back then.
eiyuu kidori itsu datte shinjita muteki no kankaku
I think I'm a hero and believe that I'm invincible.
tatakatte iru no wa chikyuu no tame nanka janai
I'm not fighting for the world.
motto mai peesu de
It's for a more personal,
sou motto shoujikina negai no tame
a more honest wish.
nando to naku kizutsuite mo
No matter how many times I'm hurt